Guide to the University Historical Material records, 1821-2012 RG0031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs, 1966-1988; RG0002 Series 2; 1.5 Linear feet
  - Jacob Burns, Mrs. Lloyd H. Elliott and Pres. Elliott, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.26)
  - Pres. Lloyd H. Elliott, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.27)
  - Pres. Elliott with a woman dressed in old clothing, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.28)
  - Pres. Elliott shaking hands with a priest, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.29)
  - Pres. Elliott presenting award to a woman, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.3)
  - Pres. Elliott with another man holding aletter, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.31)
  - Pres. Elliott posing with 5 men, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.32)
  - Pres. Elliott posing with 6 men, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.33)
  - Pres. Elliott posing with 4 men, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.34)
  - Pres. Elliott talking to 2 men, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.35)
  - Pres. Elliott posing with a man and woman, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.36)
  - A man presenting his ideas to a group of people at dinner, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.37)
  - Pres. Elliott posing with a woman and 3 men, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.38)
  - Unidentified Women, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.39)
  - Pres. Elliott with unidentified women in #40, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.4)
  - Pres. Elliott posing (Cherry Tree), 02/1974 (Box 1, Folder 1.41)
  - Pres. Elliott shaking hands with a woman, both laughing, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.42)
  - Pres. Elliott and a woman holding a book for display, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.43)
  - Pres. Elliott and a woman holding a Chemistry book, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.44)
  - Pres. Elliott leaning against a wall with arms crossed, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.45)
  - Pres. Elliott explaining his views, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.46)
  - Pres. Elliott leaning against a wall with arms crossed, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.47)
  - Pres. Elliot posing for a picture, but he wasn't ready, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.48)
  - Pres. Elliot posing for a picture, while sitting on top of desk, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.49)
  - Pres. Elliot, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.5)
  - Pres. Elliott giving out award, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.51)
  - Pres. Elliott giving out award, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.52)
  - Pres. Elliott talking to another man, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.53)
  - Pres. Elliott behind the podium, speaking, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.54)
  - Pres. Elliott giving out award, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.55)
  - Two men shaking hands, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.56)
  - Pres. Elliott in background, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.57)
  - Pres. Elliott standing behind podium laughing while two men sit watching, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.58)
  - Pres. Elliott with two men with their hands up, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.59)
  - Pres. Elliott standing behind podium laughing while audience is listening and laughing too, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.6)
  - Pres. Elliott, Bell Atlantic Corporation, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.61)
  - Dr. Lloyd Elliott, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.62)
  - Mardi Gras at Mitchell Hall, 03/1968 (Box 1, Folder 1.63)
  - Pres. Lloyd Elliot, 03/1968 (Box 1, Folder 1.64)
  - Pres. Elliot with 2 other men, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Man at podium speaking, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - Two men talking, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - Two men talking, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.4)
  - Pres. Elliot with 2 other men, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.5)
  - Man speaking behind a podium, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.6)
  - News Conference, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.7)
  - Pres. Elliott speaking behind podium, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.8)
  - Other men coming to congratulate Pres. Elliot after he speaks, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.9)
  - Men standing, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Check for 1 million dollars, 08/13/1974 (Box 1, Folder 2.11)
  - Man speaking behind podium, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.12)
  - Pres. Elliott with 2 other men, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.13)
  - Pres. Elliott speaking, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.14)
  - Man in graduation gown handing flowers to a woman, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.15)
  - Women in # 15, smiling and holding flowers, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.16)
  - Ada Elam, Ace Intern with Pres. Elliot, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - Dr. Elliott with Shah of Iran, undated (Box 1, Folder 4.1)
  - Dr. Elliott with Shah of Iran, undated (Box 1, Folder 4.2)
  - Dr. Elliott with Shah of Iran with lion, undated (Box 1, Folder 4.3)
  - Dr. Elliott with Shah of Iran, undated (Box 1, Folder 4.4)
  - Dr. Elliott with Shah of Iran and others, undated (Box 1, Folder 4.5)
  - Dr. Elliott with Shah of Iran and lion, undated (Box 1, Folder 4.6)
  - Richard H. Ross and Others, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dr. Elliott-Embassy of the Sultanate of Oman, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.1)
  - Dr. Elliott-Embassy of the Sultanate of Oman, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.2)
  - Dr. Elliott-Embassy of the Sultanate of Oman, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.3)
  - Dr. Elliott with Dr. Block, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Elliott with the Shah of Iran, and others, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.1)
  - Dr. Elliott with the Shah of Iran, and others, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.2)
  - Dr. Elliott with the Shah of Iran, and others, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.3)
  - Dr. Elliott with the Shah of Iran, and others, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.4)
  - Dr. Elliott with the Shah of Iran, and others, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.5)
  - Dr. Elliott with the Shah of Iran, and others, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.6)
  - Dr. Elliot and Shah of Iran (shaking hands), undated (Box 1, Folder 8.7)
  - Dr. Elliott with the Shah of Iran, and others, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.8)
  - Dr. Elliott and Shah of Iran, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.9)
  - Dr. Elliott with wife of Shah of Iran and lion, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.1)
  - Dr. Elliot with wife of Shah of Iran and lion, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.11)
  - Dr. Elliott with wife of Shah of Iran, and others, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.12)
  - Dr. Elliott, Dr. Ochoa, Mayor Washington, and others, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.1)
  - Pres. Elliott, Dr.Levy, Dr.Clark, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.2)
  - Mr. Friesen, Pres. Elliott, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.3)
  - Mr. Edgerton, Pres. Elliott, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.4)
  - Pres. Elliott, Mr. Bellows, Dr. Jones, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.5)
  - Mr. Friesen, Dr.Jones, Pres. Elliott, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.6)
  - Mayor Washington, Mr. Morris, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.7)
  - Pres. Elliott, Dr. Ochoa, and Dr. Dawling, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.8)
  - Dr. Harold Stevens, Dr. Ochoa and Pres. Elliott, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.9)
  - Pres. Elliott, Mr. Francis Scott, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.1)
  - Staff Marshal Wessell, Mr. Scott, and Mr. Bellows, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.11)
  - Mayor Washington, Emeritus Prof. Charles Collier, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.12)
  - Pres Elliott, Dr. Latimer, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.13)
  - Dr. Ochoa, President Elliott, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.14)
  - Dr. Jones, Dr. Clark, and Pres. Elliott, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.15)
  - Pres. Elliott, Mr. Frierson, Dr. Clark, and Mr. Edgerton, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.16)
  - Mr. Edgerton, Pres. Elliott, Miss Coclison, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.17)
  - Dr. Elliott with Reverend Robert J. Henle, S.J., undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Color slides of GW buildings, Hall of Gov't, undated (Box 1, Folder 11.1)
  - Gelman Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 11.2)
  - Marvin Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 11.3)
  - University Yard and Stuart Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 11.4)
  - Bell Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 11.5)
  - GWU Hospital, undated (Box 1, Folder 11.6)
  - Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 11.7)
  - Stuart Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 11.8)
  - Hall of Government, undated (Box 1, Folder 11.9)
  - Dr. Elliott with Pres. and Mrs. Reagan, others, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.1)
  - Dr. Elliott with Pres. and Mrs. Reagan, others, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.2)
  - Pres. and Mrs. Reagan on stage with others, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.3)
  - Pres. and Mrs. Reagan on stage with others, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.4)
  - Pres. and Mrs. Reagan on stage with others, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - Pres.Elliott and others, at Catholic Univ., undated (Box 1, Folder 13.1)
  - Pres.Elliott and others, at Catholic Univ., undated (Box 1, Folder 13.2)
  - Pres.Elliott and others, at Catholic Univ., undated (Box 1, Folder 13.3)
  - Pres.Elliott and others, at Catholic Univ., undated (Box 1, Folder 13.4)
  - Mr. Lee's car after accident, Catholic Univ., undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dean Bowles on National Business Today(ESPAN), Cathlic Univ., undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Pres. Elliott with Prime Minister of Korea, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Large Group posed, undated (Box 1, Folder 17.1)
  - Gaston Sigur, Dr. Han Lih Wu, Gen. Yeh Hsiang Chih, undated (Box 1, Folder 17.2)
  - Speaker, undated (Box 1, Folder 17.3)
  - Dr. Elliott with Bonnie Sahn and Mary Kleh, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Pres. Elliott with Lt. Gen. August Schomburg, 03/31/1966 (Box 2, Folder 1.1)
  - Lt. Gen. August Schomburg, Pres. Elliott, James Dockeray after signing agreement for Armed Forces Cooperative Program, 3/31/1966 (Box 2, Folder 1.2)
  - Reception and Dinner in Honor of Pres. Elliott, 04/27/1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Association meeting at the National Press Club, 10/28/1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Outstanding Community Service Award to GWU, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Pres. Elliott at Award Dinner, 09/26/1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - House of the Temple for Scottish Rite Luncheon, 10/06/1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Pres. Elliott with Colonel Henry L. Gordner, 11/02/1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pres.Elliott at It's Academic (Show #21), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Commencement- National Law Center, 07/01/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Pres. Elliott at subcommittee for the House District Committee, 08/26/1970 (Box 2, Folder 10.1)
  - Pres. Elliott at subcommittee for the House District Committee, 08/26/1970 (Box 2, Folder 10.2)
  - Pres. Elliott at subcommittee for the House District Committee, 08/26/1970 (Box 2, Folder 10.3)
  - Pres. Elliott at subcommittee for the House District Committee, 08/26/1970 (Box 2, Folder 10.4)
  - Pres. Elliott at Georgetown University, 09/18/1970 (Box 2, Folder 11.1)
  - Pres. Elliott at Georgetown University, 09/18/1970 (Box 2, Folder 11.2)
  - Pres. Elliott at Sesquicentennial Celebr., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12.1)
  - Pres. Elliott at Sesquicentennial Celebr., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12.2)
  - Pres. Elliott with Mr. and Mrs. Morton Bender, Dr. Alpert, 10/1971 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Pres. Elliott with Mrs. Merril Harriman and Mrs. Alice Baker, 12/08/1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - I. M. F. Tree Raising Function, 05/05/1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pres.Elliott with Senator Jennings Randolph, 08/15/1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Pres. Elliott with Dr. Seymour Alpert, 11/14/1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Portrait Proofs of Dr. Elliott, 04/09/1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Pres. Elliott with Professor Oppenheim, 06/02/1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Pres. Elliott with Dr. Alpert, 06/28/1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Pres. Elliott with Mayor Walter Washington and others, 10/12/1973 (Box 2, Folder 21.1)
  - Pres. Elliott with Mayor Washington, 10/12/1973 (Box 2, Folder 21.2)
  - Pres. Elliott with Mayor Washington and others, 10/12/1973 (Box 2, Folder 21.3)
  - Art Burns Retirement Reception, 05/03/1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Pres. Elliott with Mr. and Mrs. Jerry Lewis, 06/18/1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Pres. Elliott with Robert I. Bickford, 08/15/1974 (Box 2, Folder 24.1)
  - Pres Elliott with Robert I. Bickford and others, 08/15/1974 (Box 2, Folder 24.2)
  - Pres Elliot with Robert I. Bickford and others, 08/15/1974 (Box 2, Folder 24.3)
  - Pres. Elliott with 3 men, 08/15/1974 (Box 2, Folder 24.4)
  - Pres. Elliott with Robert I. Bickford, 08/15/1974 (Box 2, Folder 24.5)
  - Pres. Elliott and others, 08/15/1974 (Box 2, Folder 24.6)
  - Pres. Elliott with Robert I. Bickford, 08/15/1974 (Box 2, Folder 24.7)
  - Convocation, Pres. Elliott and others, 02/17/1975 (Box 2, Folder 25.1)
  - Convocation, Pres. Elliott and 2 men, 02/17/1975 (Box 2, Folder 25.2)
  - Convocation, Pres. Elliott and 2 men, 02/17/1975 (Box 2, Folder 25.3)
  - 3 men and a women in cap and gown, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.4)
  - 3 men and a women in cap and gown, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.5)
  - Speaker in cap and gown at podium, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.6)
  - Pres. Elliott and others, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.7)
  - Pres. Elliott and a man talking, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.8)
  - Convocation- Mr. Donati, Senator Fulbright, Mrs. Margaret Truman Daniel, Pres. Elliott, 02/17/1975 (Box 2, Folder 25.9)
  - Pres. Elliott with Dr. Jones and Mrs. Zelda Fichandler, all in caps and gowns, 05/04/1975 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Commencement- Mrs. Jouett Shouse, Pres. Elliott at podium, 05/04/1975 (Box 2, Folder 27.1)
  - Commencement- Dean Solomon, Mr. Joseph Fisher and Pres. Elliott, 05/04/1975 (Box 2, Folder 27.2)
  - Commencement- School of Government and Business Administration, Pres. Elliott, Mr. Leo Bernstein, Dean Vaill, 05/04/1975 (Box 2, Folder 27.3)
  - Commencement- School of Engineering, Mr. Seamans, Pres. Elliott, 05/04/1975 (Box 2, Folder 27.4)
  - Trustee Henry Clausen, Mr. Renab Camalier, Pres. Elliott, 05/04/1975 (Box 2, Folder 27.5)
  - Retirement of Dr. McGruder from CGS, 05/29/1975 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Pres. Elliott with Carolyn Fiske, 06/12/1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Pres. Elliott with the Secretary of the Organization of American States, 08/1975 (Box 2, Folder 30.1)
  - Pres. Elliott with secretary General Orfila of Organization of American States, 08/14/1975 (Box 2, Folder 30.2)
  - Pres. Elliott with Tashima Araki, Pres. Of Kyoto University, 10/16/1975 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Pres. Elliott at Dinner Tribute to Sy Albert, 12/03/1975 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Presentation of Gulf oil Foundation Check to Oppenheim, 05/21/1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - GWU Medical Commencement, 05/21/1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Naeser Retirement Dinner, 06/1976 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Pres. Elliott at Mrs. Flary's Retirement, 8/19/1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Luther Rice Luncheon, 02/03/1977 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Pres. Elliott with Dr. Chang Chi-Yun, R.C.Kuo and Sam Chang, at Taipei, Taiwan, 03/03/1977 (Box 2, Folder 38.1)
  - Pres. Elliott with Pres. R. C. Kuo and Sam Chang, Taipei, Taiwan, 03/03/1977 (Box 2, Folder 38.2)
  - Pres. Elliott with Dr.Chang Chi-Yun,Taipei,Taiwan, 03/03/1977 (Box 2, Folder 38.3)
  - Pres. Elliott with Dr. Chang Chi-Yun, Taipei,Taiwan, 03/03/1977 (Box 2, Folder 38.4)
  - Secretaries of the Treasury, June 1946-April 21,1977 (Box 2, Folder 39.1)
  - Secretaries of the Treasury, 05/16/1977 (Box 2, Folder 39.2)
  - Law School graduation, 05/22/1977 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Pres. Elliott with Dr. Thomas M. Peary, 06/1977 (Box 2, Folder 41.1)
  - Pres. Elliott with Dr. Thomas M. Peary, 06/1977 (Box 2, Folder 41.2)
  - Luther Rice Society, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 42.1)
  - Luther Rice Society, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 42.2)
  - Luther Rice Society, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 42.3)
  - Luther Rice Society, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 42.4)
  - Luther Rice Society, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 42.5)
  - Luther Rice Society, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 42.6)
  - Luther Rice Society, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 42.7)
  - Pres. Elliot's visit to Institute for Biological Studies of Tehran University, 04/10/1978 (Box 2, Folder 43.1)
  - Institute for Biological Studies, Tehran, 04/10/1978 (Box 2, Folder 43.2)
  - Tehran-flowers from Behrooz (Bob), Mohit, MBA-GWU, 04/12/1978 (Box 2, Folder 43.3)
  - Medical School Class Reunion, 05/1978 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Commencement- Maestro Rostropovich and student GW award recipients, 05/07/1978 (Box 2, Folder 45.1)
  - Commencement-Dr. Rostropovich and Dr. Brown, 05/07/1978 (Box 2, Folder 45.2)
  - Commencement- Dean Liebowitz, Pres. Elliott, GWU Donald Hearth, Langley Research Center, 05/07/1978 (Box 2, Folder 45.3)
  - Commencement- President Elliot, Robert Caldwell, and Dean Vaill of GWU, 05/07/1978 (Box 2, Folder 45.4)
  - Commencement participant relaxing, 05/1978 (Box 2, Folder 45.5)
  - Jimmy Carter with Menachem Begin outside the White House, 05/18/1978 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Mr. L.A. Jennings, award recipient, 06/26/1978 (Box 2, Folder 47.1)
  - Mr. L.A. Jennings, award recipient, 06/26/1978 (Box 2, Folder 47.2)
  - Pres. Elliott with the First Lady Jehan Sadat (Egypt), 11/10/1978 (Box 2, Folder 48.1)
  - Pres. Elliott with the First Lady Jehan Sadat (Egypt), 11/10/1978 (Box 2, Folder 48.2)
  - Pres. Elliott at International Congress Center, 04/09/1979 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Commencement- National Law Center, 05/20/1979 (Box 2, Folder 50.1)
  - Commencement, 05/06/1979 (Box 2, Folder 50.2)
  - Commencement-w/ Lee Iacocca, 05/06/1979 (Box 2, Folder 50.3)
  - Commencement-w/ F. Gutheim, H. Gillette Jr., 05/06/1979 (Box 2, Folder 50.4)
  - Commencement-Dean Robert Kramer, Nat. Law Center, 05/20/1979 (Box 2, Folder 50.5)
  - Commencement, Nat. Law Center w/ Dean Robert Kramer, H. Bright, Judge McCree Jr., 05/20/1979 (Box 2, Folder 50.6)
  - Commencement, 05/06/1979 (Box 2, Folder 50.7)
  - Two men in caps and gowns, undated (Box 2, Folder 50.8)
  - Pres. Elliott at United Way Education Division, 05/07/1979 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Pres. Elliott with Henry C. Clausen and Gen. Howard Johnson, 12/06/1979 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Pres. Elliott in front of the Gelman Library, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Pres. Elliott with Paul M.Niebell and 2 others, 03/28/1980 (Box 2, Folder 54.1)
  - Pres. Elliott with Paul M.Niebell and 3 others, 03/28/1980 (Box 2, Folder 54.2)
  - Luncheon at Mr. Kronheims, 07/01/1980 (Box 2, Folder 55.1)
  - Luncheon at Mr. Kronheims, with Milton Kronheim and Judge David Bazelon, 07/01/1980 (Box 2, Folder 55.2)
  - Luther Rice Society Annual Affair, 11/07/1980 (Box 2, Folder 56.1)
  - Dedication of Himmelfarb Portrait, 11/09/1980 (Box 2, Folder 56.2)
  - GWU ClubSpring, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Pres. Elliott at a meeting of Council on Post Secondary Accredition, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Pres. Elliott with Mrs. Bloedorn, 03/04/1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - President for-a-Day Ruthie Penn, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Pres.and Mrs. Elliott with Colonel and Mrs. Thomas E. Shaefer, 05/10/1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Walcott Award presented to Pres. Elliott, 03/26/1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Pres. Elliott at the University of Pennsylvania, 08/09/1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - President Elliott-contact sheet, 02/07/1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.1)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.2)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.3)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.4)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.5)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.6)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.7)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.8)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.9)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.1)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.11)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.12)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.13)
  - Gilbert Stuart Reception-Presentation Ceremony, 01/28/1983 (Box 3, Folder 8.14)
  - Vocation- Pres. Elliott and others, 02/21/1983 (Box 3, Folder 9.1)
  - Convocation-Pres. Elliott with Alumni Achievement Award-Ming Chen HSU and others, undated (Box 3, Folder 9.2)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.1)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.2)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.3)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.4)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.5)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.6)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.7)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.8)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.9)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.1)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.11)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.12)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.13)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.14)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.15)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.16)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.17)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.18)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.19)
  - Woodhull House and Old President's House, 05/05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 10.2)
  - Pres. Elliott with Secretary Coleman and Prof. Gilliam, 09/29/1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Pres. Elliott with Richard Allens and family, 02/21/1983 (Box 3, Folder 12.1)
  - Pres. Elliott with Richard Allens and family, 02/21/1983 (Box 3, Folder 12.2)
  - Pres. Elliott and others, 11/09/1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Pres. Elliott and others, 11/14/1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Pres. Elliot with Lim Y. II Nam (Korea), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Convocation- Seymour & Ceil Alpert & Pres. Elliott, 02/20/1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Faculty/Student Basketball Game, 03/27/1984 (Box 3, Folder 17.1)
  - Faculty/Student Basketball Game, 03/27/1984 (Box 3, Folder 17.2)
  - GWU Spring symposium on Health Sciences -Pres. Elliott, Sen. Dole and others, 03/27/1984 (Box 3, Folder 18.1)
  - GWU Spring symposium on Health Sciences- Pres. Elliott,Dr. Allan L. Goldstein, and Sen. Dole, 03/27/1984 (Box 3, Folder 18.2)
  - Pres. Elliott with Indonesians- at golf course, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19.1)
  - Pres. Elliott with Indonesians- at golf course, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19.2)
  - Pres. Elliott with Indonesians- at golf course, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19.3)
  - Pres. Elliott with Indonesians- at golf course, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19.4)
  - Pres. Elliott with Indonesians- at golf course, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19.5)
  - Pres. Elliott with Indonesians- at golf course, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19.6)
  - Pres. Elliott and a man sitting and talking next to a sculpture, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19.7)
  - Pres. Elliott and a man sitting and talking next to a sculpture, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19.8)
  - Convocation9/12/1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 20.1)
  - Convocation, People sitting on stage, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 20.2)
  - Convocation, People sitting on stage, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 20.3)
  - Convocation Pres. Elliott at podium, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 20.4)
  - Convocation Pres. Elliott at podium, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 20.5)
  - Tibetan Monk Visit, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Pres. Elliott at Conference at Airlie House, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - The Elliotts and Colangelos and Mrs. Amling at Football Game (Cowboys vs Redskins), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23.1)
  - The Elliotts and Colangelos and Mrs. Amling at Football Game (Cowboys vs Redskins), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23.2)
  - Prof. and Mrs. Frederick Amling at luncheon preceding Dallas Cowboys- Washington Redskins game, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23.3)
  - Pres. Elliott and Mrs. Francis J. Lyons at preceding Dallas Cowboys-Washington Redskins game, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23.4)